# Fiachra Holland

Email: <a href="mailto:fiachraholland@gmail.com">fiachraholland@gmail.com</a>

DOB: 01/11/89 Phone: +353 83 064 8173

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a very capable person who learns fast and doesn't need to be shown the same thing twice. I have lived and worked in four countries on two continents over the past ten years, and I have garnered many different work and life experiences along the way. I always strive to find the most efficient and ergonomic solution to everything I do and I feel like I would be a welcome addition to any team.

### **EDUCATION**

# European Baccalaureate at Sancta Maria College

September 2002 - June 2008 Passed the Irish Leaving Certificate.

Credit Course at the University of Edinburgh September 2016 - June 2017

I studied 6 credit courses including politics, philosophy and literature.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

**Agent at Capita Customer Solutions** *July 2018 - Present - Clonakilty, Co.Cork -* I am currently working for the outsourcing company Capita as a case assessment officer on a government contract. Prior to this role I was working as a finance and collections agent on a telecommunications contract, working for both the consumer and corporate teams and was consistently a top performer.

Office Worker at Assistans Konsult Gruppen August 2017 - May 2018 - Stockholm - I worked in the office of a financial consultancy firm in Stockholm. My main duties included website maintenance and modification, assistant consulting and general office work.

Assembly Line Operator at Bombardier Recreational Products Finland OY June 2012 - June 2016 - Rovaniemi, Northern FInland - I worked on the assembly line on one of Europe's most advanced assembly lines. I worked on the final assembly & packaging lines, adhering to strict timing and quality controls. This was a high paced job which required quick thinking & attention to detail.

Vine pruner at Brooklyn Valley Wines February 2012 - June 2012 - Margaret River, Western Australia I worked on an award winning vine farm for one season in order to acquire my second year working holiday visa in Australia. I was the main pruner during this season. I was trained to use specialized electric pruning equipment and also the correct way to prune vines to award winning quality. I was also responsible for the upkeep and installation of new irrigation systems on the farm.

**Skilled Labourer at Fluid Building Services** *November 2010 - January 2012 - Sydney -* I worked as a skilled labourer, generally on high rise apartment building renovations in the center of Sydney. Duties included waterproofing, bricklaying, basic plumbing, and various other construction jobs.

(I have also worked various construction/hospitality jobs from an early age in Ireland that are not listed here)

## **INTERESTS**

Chess, guitar, travelling and language study and are my main interests in my free time.

## **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

Full, clean Irish driving license.

Manual Handling Certificate.

Safe pass.